[music]
[snorts]
All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful Wednesday afternoon. It is a
beautiful afternoon, I have to say. The
sun is shining, the birds are shining,
the grass is chirping, the sun is green,
there's not a cloud in the sky. Okay.
Actually, there are lots of clouds in
the sky, but there's not a cloud on the
ground. All right. Blessings to
everybody in the name of Jesus Yeshua
the Messiah. I pray you guys are super
blessed. All right. Now, uh what is
going on, guys? You know, I'm in a
little bit of a long trade here over on
Bitbase. All right. Bitbase, which by
the way, is giving away $500 a week,
baby. $500 a week. In fact, today we're
going to be giving away $500 courtesy of
Bitbase. So, if you want to win $500
today, simply subscribe. Not subscribe.
Yeah, subscribe to the dang channel, but
sign up to Bitbase using the link in the
description. It won't cost you a dang
thing. All right. Also, guys, a quick
reminder that Blow Fin is giving away
$2,000 a week as well. So, if you want a
chance to win $2,000 every single week,
guys, we're giving away $2,500 a week on
these live streams. All right? So, make
sure to sign up to Blowofin. Again, you
don't have to deposit anything. All
right, you do not have to deposit
anything. Bitcoin is coming up right now
to a little area of resistance. All
right, the short setup given in the
Casper crew this morning. It's so funny.
We had two trades this morning. The long
trade given live in the Casper crew VIP
Discord during the New York open live
stream where we longed this low on the
back test of the golden pocket. And now
we're coming right up to our short zone
numero uno right into the short setup
given in the Casper crew VIP discord
over at jasonaspertrading.com.
Sheesh man. I am the J Schillington.
They call me Jason Schillington. I'm
just here to sell you guys my stuff. I'm
here to sell you guys my stuff. I don't
even know what a dang candlestick is.
You know what I'm saying? [laughter]
Big shout out to everybody in the chat.
Shout out to Nico. Why so choppy? We'll
talk about it. Honestly, we'll talk
about Do I buy spot Bitcoin? Heck yes, I
buy spot Bitcoin. Cryptomind 64.
Cryptomind 64. Let me just tell you, I
cut my teeth on spot Bitcoin way back in
the beginning. Way back in the beginning
when I was just a young crypto guy with
a dream, I put my whole life savings in
spot bitcoin and I still have a large
portion of my net worth in spot bitcoin.
All right. I I have close to half of my
net worth in
crypto in bitcoin really. I mean in
bitcoin and and crypto assets. Let's
just put it that way.
Um, but yeah, seriously, short signal
given, but you're in a long short signal
setup was given, my friend. The setup
was given this morning. The signal,
which by the way is not financial
advice, was given this morning during
the New York open liveream. So, the New
York open live stream, what happened
this morning was we were looking for a
long trade from down here in the Cash
Pro Crew VIP where we, you know, every
single week we're in there multiple
times a day, literally going through the
live price action. I was looking to long
here. Okay. But then what happened is we
took the liquidity and we got a reclaim,
right? We got a reclaim and we got a
fast pump. And I'm like, man, missed
opportunity, baby. But I'm like, you
know what? You know what? Given the
context of the market, given the context
of as we came and we made this low, we
had really bullish looking divergence
right here. You know, I said if we come
back down to the Fibonacci golden
pocket, then I'll take a long. Well,
during the live stream, we came down to
the Fibonacci golden pocket.
As you can see right here, if we zoom in
right on that first back test, right
into the Fibonacci golden pocket here,
that's where I fired off the old juicy
long trade. Hit a TP1,
I've closed half the dang trade,
and now, well, we still have half the
trade open. We're up right now over
We're up like seven grand. Seven grand.
My goodness, that's crazy. Okay, that is
crazy. So, yeah, short setup given, long
setup given, but the only one that I
publicly took was this one right here.
Okay, and I'm going to tell you why.
Well, first of all, I am in a short
trade already. I've been short on
Antarctic for quite some time. All
right, holding the short trade, but I'm
going to I'm going to be talking about
exactly what I think is going to happen.
Big shout out to uh bullish on parade.
Hey, buddy and fellow humans. Jay, hope
you didn't close your short from the
top. We're going to go way lower. Well,
I'm not really in a short from the top.
I'm in a short from pretty much right
around where we're at now.
I was short from around $65,000.
So, yeah, there's a good chance, guys,
that you know, here's the thing. Right
now, we are attempting to break out of
this trend line right here. As you can
see, if we can break out of this trend
line, guys, we can go to $67,000.
All right, we absolutely can go to
67,000.
Um,
shout out to Zavididi. Zavidi Vorlex.
Bitcoin has been front running levels up
and down lately. Seriously, man. It's
been chop city.
$500 or 500 two week future trial
voucher. A $500 of uh money that you can
trade with but cannot withdraw. All
right. You can trade with the $500. You
can't withdraw it. All right. But I
don't I think it la I don't think it has
an an expository an a suppository a
suppository date. All right. I don't
think it has a suppository date. You
know what I'm saying? Shout out to CBK.
Wahoo. And shout out to the real Bay TC.
Shout out to your boy Black Swan. He
says Romans 831. Good morning Jay. Good
morning to you. Good afternoon and dump
we trust. I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Big shout out to Iris Fox 6641. Big
shout out to Sigma Crypto 3253. Big
shout out to Ilrich 69. PBLL who says
yellow. Shout out to RP Pink in the
house. What is going on? R Pink in the
house, my man. In the house. It expires
within 2 weeks. All right. I didn't know
that. I thought it lasted forever. But
you know what? Then use it in two weeks,
guys. If you have $500 to trade in two
weeks, use in two weeks. All right. And
guess what? If you're not interested in
$500 to trade with in two weeks, then
don't participate in the juicy
giveaways.
All right,
but seriously, if you're into some
actual cash giveaways, if you want some
actual cash giveaways, smash up the dang
likes. All right, we have 400 people in
the house. If we could get we let's
let's let's give it a real target. If we
can get 500 likes, we're almost at 500
viewers. If we can get 500 likes within
the first 45, I'll do an actual cash
giveaway. And if you want juicy cash
giveaways, join the Casper Crew VIP
Discord. All right, last month we
literally gave away like $10,000 of
actual money, actual cash. All right,
actual cash.
So, you want some real giveaways, join
the VIP Discord. Not only do you get the
juicy trade, not signals like this long
trade right here or this long trade
right here up 40 grand which was given
in advance and in the moment on June
25th, but we're giving away cash. We're
just throwing we're paying you to stay,
you know? I mean, what's more valuable?
Having followers or having money? and
obviously followers, you know, cuz
nothing can scratch the the the
self-esteem the low self-esteem itch
like having likes and subscribes on
YouTube and Twitter. So, make sure to
like me on Twitter and and and follow me
on on on Facebook and and on on MySpace
and YouTube
and all those cool social media apps
that you young children are into these
days. All right. Um, should we really
take partial profits? Isn't that just a
means of easing the mind? Yes, it's a
means of easing the mind. Mr. Darkness
revealed 8630. Look, trading is 99%
psychology. Any idiot can spend 3 months
on YouTube and know everything about
trading. Any idiot can watch 3 months of
YouTube videos. Any idiot can go to the
Jason Casper YouTube channel right here.
Any idiot can go to playlists. And any
idiot can click the free course where I
give away more information for free than
most paid courses give away charging you
thousands of dollars and know everything
about trading. But here's the thing.
Knowing and doing are two different
things. And the barrier between knowing
and doing is literally your psychology.
All right? It's the trading psychology
that literally will make or break you as
a trader. Okay? And so taking partial
profits, what does this do? It allows
you to relax. It allows you to see
clearly. It allows you to make small and
consistent profits over time without
letting the fear and greed cloud your
decision-making. And so by taking
partial profits, you can be more
profitable over time. Not because you
couldn't in theory be more profitable
taking one profit at the exact top after
you long the exact bottom,
but because your psychology puts you in
a position where you actually mentally
can handle letting the trades ride a
little bit longer, not taking a trade
right now when you know you shouldn't
because it's not the best trade to take,
but you have that FOMO because you're
not in a position.
You guys know what I'm saying?
You guys know what I'm saying? You know.
Um,
but but
yeah, I Yeah, this guy says, "As the
biggest idiot, I can confirm this true."
And as an idiot myself, I can confirm
this is true. All right. Two days on
YouTube, one video about support and
resistance and bullish divergences. Man,
I'm an expert, man. What do they call
that? The Grundling Krueger effect or
whatever. The Ghouly Krueger effect.
What is that effect where you where you
watch one YouTube video and you think
you're an expert?
What's my top supplements [music]
that me or a person should take? That
has nothing to do with crypto.
But if you have to know, it's obviously
got to be
uh if you're not getting your omega-3s
through your diet, omega-3, if you're
not getting vitamin D from the zone,
vitamin D, if you take vitamin D, you
got to take it with vitamin K. uh make
sure you're not deficient in magnesium
or copper or selenium or iodine. Really,
it's you have to find out if you're
deficient in if you're deficient. The
the purpose of a supplement is to reduce
the deficiency. And ideally, you should
be able to just eat your diet, right?
For me personally, a big fan of
magnesium blyinate. A big fan of
glycine.
A big fan of cod liver oil andor some
kind of DHA supplement if I'm not eating
fatty fish on a regular basis. A big fan
of an iodine supplement if
I I've always had issues with low
thyroid in my life. So the iodine for me
that could affect your thyroid. All
right? So make sure you're getting
iodine. I don't eat table salt. Um,
that's really about it really.
Um, I'm trying to think. Yeah, those are
the big ones. Vitamin D,
magnesium,
glycine, and if you struggle with high
cortisol because you're stressed out and
all this, ashwagandha
in in phases can be really good for
helping you get your sleep. Glycine and
ashwagandha. There you go. All right,
now let's let's pop into the actual
Bitcoin chart, guys. All right, let's
pop into the actual Bitcoin chart. This
was from the video I made yesterday. I
want to start on the weekly time frame
because honestly, I want to start on the
twoe time frame right now, guys. Yeah,
we're long on Bitcoin right now. All
right, from the from the Dang Casper
Crew VIP Discord. All right, we're up
seven grand.
We're up seven grand. Um,
but let's see.
Let's see.
Here's the deal, guys. twoe time frame.
We we we the the the elephant in the
room is this. Let's go to the all-time
index, guys. The elephant in the room is
we are confirming we have confirmed
officially a good old-fashioned uneven
butt cheek pattern on the twoe. All
right, as the price is getting lower to
the macro Fibonacci golden pocket, the
oscillator right here, we have a juicy
left momentum wave and a skinny right
momentum wave. On the twoe, we've
confirmed a bit boy green dot
with an oversold wave. Then we confirmed
a higher wave. All right, giving us the
juicy uneven butt cheek pattern. Big on
the left, skinny on the right, coming
out looking like Dolores from the diner
as the price is getting lower to key
support. She's waddling out here,
spilling the dang coffee all over the
floor with those uneven glutius maxim.
And then boom, the price starts to get
moved to the upside. Now, the question
is, does this mean the bottom of the
bare market is in? There are some who
will make the argument, yes, the bottom
of the bare market is in. The only way
you could possibly make the argument
that the bottom of the bare market is in
if we're going on past data is the
confirmed bullish divergence. Okay,
that's the only possible way because the
last time we had this exact signal, the
bottom wasn't. Now, that being said, in
the past, every single bottom happens at
least 365 days after the all-time high.
All these green boxes on the Bitcoin
alltime index are the past cycles where
we bottomed out. And the green vertical
line is 365 days after the all-time
high. What does that mean? It means we
have about two months, guys. About two
months until the bottom is in. If we're
going to go based on the historic data
of the 4-year cycle after the all-time
high. Now, I do want to point out
something else about these indicators
that mark the bottom. Every time the
indicator marks the bottom, it actually
becomes
[snorts] it's it's like a drug. And each
time you need a stronger dose of the
drug to get you out of the bottom. The
first time we just needed an oversold
wave. All right. The second time we
needed an oversold wave with a big
Bitcoin green dot. All right. The third
time we need an oversold wave with a big
Bitcoin green dot and a bullish
divergence.
Now, I'm just saying each time the
bottom signals in, it has to be a little
bit more bullish looking than the last
time. What would make this one even more
bullish? A third drive of divergence.
Honestly, maybe this time it does this.
I don't know. Maybe this time we have to
get the triicular formation. What's the
triular formation, you ask? The
triicular formation is something like
this. All right, let me show you a
classic triular.
All right, a triular formation. Perfect
example back from April 2025.
Is the bottom in? Is the bottom in? We
have a bullish divergence on the daily
time frame, right? uneven butt cheek
pattern. Clearly, Dolores is at the
diner. Clearly, it's not her day off.
Clearly, she's coming to the table.
Clearly, the price is even getting a
bounce. But then what happens? We make a
lower low. And we form another butt
cheek. The triicular formation. All
right. One, two, three. All right. Also
known as pseudocracatus. The pseudoratus
in Latin, which basically means fake
butt crack in English. because you would
assume this is the butt crack, but
you're wrong. It's simply just a big
dimple of cellulite in the left butt
cheek, a massively large butt crack in
the middle, followed by the right cheek.
And if we take the measuring tool from
cheek to cheek, we're actually measuring
about 31 days of crack. 31 days of crack
will drive anybody crazy. 31 days of
crack could kill you. It probably will
kill you. 31 days of crack you don't
want to mess with. And look at what
happens after the 31 days of crack.
That's when the actual bottom is in.
Boom.
Okay, now coming back to our two-weekly,
we have to ask, is there a triicular on
our horizon? Well, obviously only time
will tell,
but if we're going to look at all the
data together, we do have to say that
historically speaking, it's 365 days
after the all-time high where we bottom
out. And historically speaking, each
signal on market cyb needs to get a
little bit stronger than last time. Does
that mean the bottom can't be a no? No,
the bottom could be a no. And I've been
very open about the fact that I am I am
I have bought Bitcoin on spot down here.
And I've been very honest about the fact
that if you're on the sideline and you
have no Bitcoin,
we are objectively speaking at a 50%
discount right now, which is a good
place to buy any asset. If you want to
buy anything, let's say you you had a
dream car, a dream car, all of a sudden
it goes on sale 50% off. Would you say,
"Eh, nah, I'll wait for it to go lower."
No. You would buy at least half of that
car. or you you might buy a third of
that car. You might go into the
dealership and saw a third of that car
off and purchase a third of that car.
[music] And if it goes even lower, then
you might go buy the other 2/3. That's
how I'm approaching Bitcoin right now.
I'm breaking into the dealership at
night. I'm vandalizing the vehicle. I'm
cutting it into pieces and I'm buying
just a little bit at a time. Right now
is a good time to start buying into
Bitcoin. Now, I'm going to be building a
position so long as we're under $70,000.
The lower we go, the more I buy. All
right. Now, as we get to the weekly time
frame, what else do we see here? We see
bullish divergences as well. Very
interesting. Now, let's go to the daily
time frame. This is where things get
really interesting. The daily time frame
right now is confirming an ultra bullish
signal here which is a classic a classic
market cipher
uh signal which is this a big bottom
very oversold with a double bit boy big
ben green dot aka snake eyes. All right
followed by the price making a lower low
into the macro 618 by the way. Right.
The low we made down here at 57K is the
macro bare market bottom to bull market
top 618. We have a bullish divergence
with continued bitboy green dottage.
After that, what happens? The money flow
crosses the zero line from the purple
into the blue.
That is a very bullish signal. And now
we have a confirmed trigger wave as the
money flow is getting thicker with the
yellow oscillator pointing straight up.
This is a very bullish continuation
signal. And if I was a betting man,
which technically I am, I would assume
that the Bitcoin price at least is going
to have to go to the top of this local
range here, right? Cuz we have the
confirmed continuation pattern here. And
we have our low, our lower low forming a
very nice bottom of the bullish
divergence. And now we've made a higher
low. And it's not, honestly, I have to
say it's not the best level in the
world. Like I don't really necessarily
like this level. I would have liked for
us to come down a little bit lower to
60,000.
I was really looking for us to come down
here, but I've been saying the whole
time if we confirm that trigger wave on
the daily, I'm going to have to become
more bullishly biased because it is a
macro bullish continuation pattern,
right? [music]
I can't argue with the chart. You know,
I might want to come lower here. We're
up right now five grand, guys. Do you
see this? We're up right now five grand,
but we're up. We're up eight eight nine.
We're up $9,000. $9,000.
Wow. Look at this. We are breaking out
the dang resistance, baby. From the
trade setup I've given live in the
Casper Crew New York open live stream
this morning. We sniped the dang entry
in real time at jasonaspertrading.com.
Right from the back test.
I can't even take myself seriously,
guys. We sniped the entry.
We sniped the entry right from the back
test of this uh golden pocket. Can you
even spot it? The dang golden pocket.
Can you spot it? I love pulling my fib
out. Let's pull the fib out right here.
Zoop. Right from the dang 618. Would you
look at that? Right from the dang 618.
Amazing.
Fantastic. We're breaking out of the
trend line, guys. We're breaking out the
dang trend line. Wow.
That is crazy. That is pretty crazy.
That is pretty crazy. Is this not Is
this not crazy? We locked in a juicy.
This could be the next big one. This
could be the next big one. All right,
this could be the next big one. I'm not
going to lie.
All right, it might not be the next big
one. We'll have to wait and see what
happens, guys. It really might not be.
We'll honestly have to wait and see what
happens. All right. Um, don't fade the
fib, baby. Shoulder, head, shoulder,
baby. Mad how we topped out around that
1.618 fib extension and now finding
support at the 618.
You're up 5K in a long, but you're
telling people about your short setup.
Yes. Yes, [laughter]
of course. Cuz look, over in the Casper
crew, man, we trade the markets up and
down. Like, what the heck, bro? I long
and short and I'm literally in a short
right now. I'm literally in a short
right now as well. I'm in a short right
now. It's up 100 bucks. It's up 200
bucks short, baby, on Bitcoin. All
right. Yeah. Yeah. I'm telling people
about my short setup and I'm long. I'm
in multiple longs. This long right here,
given in advance, in the moment, told
people when I'm taking it, up 40 grand.
This long trade here, I told everybody
exactly when I was taking it. We made
the plan. We took it live. I don't know
what else to tell you. Yeah, I'm telling
people about my dang short setup. Why am
I telling about my short setup? Cuz look
at where we came up to.
Like today, right today, there was one
short I'm looking for. Where do you come
up to? We come up to there. That if you
were going to short today, that was the
place to short. If you're going to take
a short today, it was from here. You
could have made money on that short
trade. We got a 0.5% move on that first
tap. That's a pretty significant move.
Not going to lie,
you know. 5% move in my opinion. That's
a pretty good scalp, you know. That's a
pretty dang good scalp,
you know. I'm shorting 653. Okay. Shout
out to Felix H. He says, "Bonjour Jason
from the south of France. I'm staying at
an amazing countryside location with
vineyards and chickens. That's what's
up.
That's what's up. Weekly inverted head
and shoulders. This could be it. Shout
out to J Boy Bullish. Shout out to R
Pink. Shout out to Persita Sharma. ETH
is pumping. Everything's pumping, guys.
Have you seen the dang stock market
lately? Have you seen E the ES? Look at
this nonsense.
Look at yesterday's candle.
Look at this. I mean, yeah, today's a
little bit of a purple back test, but
look at that. Everything's kind of
pumping lately. The gold pumped like
crazy. Look at gold, man. Look at gold.
[music]
Oh my goodness. Would you look at gold?
It's amazing. Let's check out Ethereum.
Wow. Etherum
doing some crazy stuff, man. Let's
actually take a look at Etherum here.
Okay, guys. I have to say like what else
can I say besides ETH is holding above
this macro PC. That is not bearish.
Let's go ahead and put on the twoe
oscillator for ETH.
Um,
let's check out the weekly. Now, the
weekly market site for beyond ETH, I do
have to say looks absolutely beautiful.
It looks absolutely gorgeous. We have a
nice bullish divergence. Money flow
getting higher. We bounced perfectly
from value area low. We've reclaimed the
PC of the range. In my opinion, the next
target, dare I say it, man, I don't even
want to say it cuz you guys are going to
thumbs down me for being bullish. It's
so funny, man. You could come out on
YouTube and be bullish. You could be
bearish. People hate it because they
just want you to say what they're
thinking. So, us YouTubers, we have to
walk a very fine line. You know, well,
you know, IT COULD BE BEARISH, BUT you
know, it could be bullish. Look, it
could go up or it could be down. You
know, in fact, the best technique if
you're a YouTuber is to say something
like this.
Bitcoin is 100% going to break out and
go higher this week. Give it some time,
rest.
then say Bitcoin is 100% going to break
down and go much lower this week.
Now I just give myself two perfect
clips. Next week I'm going to come out
and talk about how I WAS RIGHT. YOU
SHOULD listen to me. Make sure TO
SUBSCRIBE TO MY CHANNEL. Make sure to
pay for my paid group. If you also want
to be right every single week, the
Casper Crew, baby. That's where it's at.
THAT'S WHERE IT'S AT. The Casper Crew.
Man, I'm getting shivers down my spine
just thinking about how right I am.
It's amazing.
But here's the thing. Honestly, the fact
that ETH is hanging up above this PC,
we could very easily get our move up to
the Fibonacci golden pocket value area
high, which is around 3,500. Like,
because also when you and I'm not saying
it's 100% going to happen, guys. I know
it sounds crazy right now. It really
does. But you have to think of it, guys.
We are forming a bullish falling wedge
into support. If we like hold above this
level, we could see a squeeze. Now,
would I prefer the bottom to be in now
for Bitcoin underneath? Honestly, I
would not. I want us to come lower for
all these assets, right? Cuz it just
makes more sense. But you know what else
makes sense? A lackluster bull market
followed by a lackluster bare market
where the bottom comes in and takes
everyone by surprise. That also makes
sense. And really, if we're going to go
based on the sideways range here, it's
very interesting. We have ourselves our
low, our lower low, then our back test,
right? We have this very clear support
that we've tested four times with a
bullish divergence on the weekly. The
last time ETH had a bullish dip on the
weekly was never a go. ETH has never had
a bullish divergence on the weekly
before. Never. Isn't that crazy? Isn't
that crazy?
4 day looking decent. 3-day looking
decent. So, here's the deal.
Honestly, with ETH right now, the the re
like
I You know what? This is getting me a
little bit bullish, you know. This is
getting me a little bit bullish.
Clip that. Clip that. You know, also
this is getting me a little bit bearish.
Clip that, too. We have changed market
structure here actually like very
locally. You could you you know,
obviously we changed market structure
here very locally as well, right? But
this is like a flip of a PC. What I
would really like is maybe a triple
bottom here would be really really nice.
Like if we could get this thing to look
more like an accumulation range,
that would be really really nice. You
know, where we take that low one more
time, we come and we we take this
liquidity, we tap into value area low
one more time. That would be really
really nice here. Maybe we could do that
within the next few months. Maybe ETH
does get a rise and it ends up being a
bull trap and we just take like this. We
reject from here and then we come down
again. We take the lows and then we come
back inside the range. We make a higher
low and then boom. Right? That would
actually look like a really nice
accumulation range at the bottom. Right?
form our base of support,
do a liquidity grab at the local high,
bull trap, come back down, bear trap,
you know, test that low again with a
lower low, and then basically
get this whole invert head and shoulder
thing going. That would be a really nice
low for ETH. All right, now let's check
out.
Wow, look at this, man. Look at this.
Bitcoin pumping like a wild lady in
distress right now. You look after a
week of this. After a week of Chop City,
man, this is a pump. I have to say like
after a week of nothing, this is a pump
right now. I mean, we go to the one
minute chart here. I mean, would you
look at these two massively green
candles?
Wow. The one minute's getting me stoked.
Is it getting you guys stoked? If it is,
make sure to smash up the dang likes,
you know? Um,
sorry Vortex, I don't mean to give you
extreme FOMO, man. But [music] look, I
always have FOMO myself.
You know, market makers are nice. They
love giving people what they need.
[music] Is that true? What What do
people need? We need We need liquidity,
baby. I'm going to short from 64. Should
I take a loss? I don't know. I'm going
to short from right around here. I'm
going to short from
647.
I'm going to short from here. So, look,
it's up to you. It's up to you. I'm I'm
willing to let this short get stopped
out, by the way, for a break even. This
short is going to stop me out for about
$4,000. cuz it'll stop me out at a break
even cuz I've already locked in four
grand on the trade.
It's up to you. Are you bullish or are
you bearish? If you're bearish and you
have a plan for your trade, then don't
close it. If you're gambling and you
don't have a plan for your trade, I
would close it. And then I would go to
the Jason Casper YouTube channel and
check out the free course. All right? If
you didn't have a plan and you're just
gambling, go to the Jason Casper YouTube
channel, go to playlists, go to the
Jason Casper free trading course, and
watch all 18 sessions, and then you'll
be able to answer your own question. All
right? You'll be able to answer your own
question. All right? And then after
that, you can watch this video on how to
lose your your love handles. The real
truth on how to get rid of your love
handles. Do you guys see this here?
The real truth on how to get rid of your
love handles is also going to be down
here. Okay? Well, actually, only if it
you're me, okay? Because YouTube thinks
I like fitness content. YouTube thinks I
want to know how to get rid of my love
handles. Cuz the one thing that plagues
me is my massive love handles. They're
so big. It's crazy. I could be skinny
everywhere, but then all of a sudden the
love handles
and they're uneven. The left side is
massive just like this left butt cheek
right here. And and then the right love
handle is so skinny just like this woman
right here at the diner. You know, the
love handles are uneven.
Isn't that crazy?
Hey yo, my love handle so uneven. They
don't call me Jason, but they call me
Steven. The left side is so fat that I'm
grieving, but I think I could lose
[music] it. I'm believing. All I got to
do is cut the calories down low. Bitcoin
price pumping. [singing] Better look out
below. The market [music] maker, his
name is that Joe. He says, "Hey Jay, we
about to go blast the resistance."
[music]
Bitcoin goes the distance. Get into the
car, push the gas on pistons. Don't you
know you can't kiss this or diss this? J
[music] Cer, we cannot reverse this.
We're coming in Antarctic. Negative 100K
like a spark tick. [music]
We got the ticks on the chart. The blue
and purple candles like a nice work of
art. Big shout to bit [music] base. What
do you say? They're giving away $500
today courtesy of your boy. His name is
Mr. [music] J Casper the same exact way.
And we also got a big shout to blow fin.
Get it in with a crypto spin [music]
with your double chin every single week.
2,000 giveaway Jason Casper blow fin
[music] giveaway
a lucky four winners they win the money
baby they could go for dinner my
favorite [music] old group [singing]
from the 60s is the spinners but Jason
Casper is looking like a winner oh man
look [music] at this guy so cool he's
got the hair metal sunglasses and
mustache too and yeah don't you know the
[music] action looking muddy trans
non-carbon binary gender studies uh back
in college [music] Jason Casper looking
like this getting knowledge [__] But
then I had to ditch the makeup and pink
hair. I even had to start wearing men's
underwear. Cuz when you're $3,000 in
debt, can't get a job, you're stuck in
the net. So I started to trade. Started
to make money. [music] Started digging
with the spade in the garden. Hey baby
Jay in the house trading Bitcoin here
[music] for the Bitcoin bounce. And oh
snap, can we take a peek? Does Marcus
Cipher B have any uneven butt cheeks?
Big on the [music] left side. So dang
juicy. Skinny on the right side to round
out the booty. And I don't even know if
[music] you could spot it, but this
morning we bounced right from the golden
pocket. Just top it. Oh man. Wow.
Amazing.
Sheesh,
man. The love handles get me so stoked
on that beat, I'll tell you. Um,
yeah. Ether. Sheesh. Shout out to
Piccioe.
Wait, how do you say that? Pick Uraso.
Picoraso.
Why didn't I participate in the world
trading competition on Bybit
Casper Crew? We were number 14 in the
world on Bybit back in 2023, I think.
Were we 14? Were we number 14 or were we
24 or were we 34? I forget. We were
actually pretty good. We were actually
pretty good. And for Blofin, what were
we on Blofin? What were we on Blofin?
I think we're pretty good on blowoff
fin.
I don't I don't officially trade on by
bit anymore. I do trade on buy bit, but
not officially anymore.
That's why. Um
but but yeah, you know. All right, let's
see. We're up five grand on this trade.
We're down $60 on this short trade, but
we're up 23,000 on this long trade. If
this stops me out, it'll stop me out for
a $4,000 profit. So, I'll be on a $100
loss. Net profit of like 30 grand. So,
not so bad. Here we go, baby. I got my
stop loss at 655. This is the make it or
break it territory. Come on, Bitcoin.
Guys, don't forget we're giving away
$500 courtesy of Bitbase today.
So, if you want a chance to win $500 on
Bitface, make sure to sign up. Link in
the description. Also, every single week
on Blowin, we're giving away $2,000.
And uh yeah, if you're interested, guys,
check it out. Check it out. Check it
out. Check it out. Check it out. Check
it out. Check it out. Check it out.
Check it out. Check it out. Check it
out. Check How's Cardano looking to me?
You know what, Juan Estrada? You got to
go and watch Crypto Crow. Cryptocrow has
all the Cardano answers. All right.
What can I say about Cardano besides the
fact that I do think it's a good project
and it's ultra bottomed out. All right.
Now, here here what I'm about to say,
and don't don't let anyone misunderstand
me here.
Right now, Cardano is 19 cents, guys.
All right. If we ever get back to our
all-time high, which I don't think is
unreasonable,
we're talking about 1,500% gain. Okay?
If you think Cardano has a future at
all, objectively speaking, it's a good
price. All right, the monthly time frame
right now is giving us a green dot. Last
time we got a green dot on the monthly,
oversold like this, it was the bare
market bottom pretty much, right? It was
the bare market bottom pretty much. We
pumped up not to a new all-time high,
but we still pumped up almost 500%. We
are about to confirm at the end of
August. Another green dot. All right,
two week market cipher B. We have a
bullish divergence. The last bullish
divergence we had was the bottom. All
right. Uh I'm sorry it wasn't the
bottom. We had one more low. But even
still, if you had bought at this
divergence, you would have pretty much
bought the bottom. If you believe in
Cardano at all, the chart is bottomed
out with bullish signals. That's all I
can say. If you think Charles Rokinson
is has quit Twitter and quit crypto and
he's quit crypto quip quitter and he's
32 but he looks 70, you're like, you
know what, how much longer can this
project go? Then don't buy it. All
right? Then don't buy it. But but
honestly, if you're if you have any kind
of bullish inclinations about Cardano,
this thing has a lot of upside. It has a
lot of upside potential and it's not a
piece of crap project either. It's
really not. All right. I lost a million
in Cardano. That coin destroyed me.
That's crazy, you know. Um,
but here's the thing. Carla says, "Come
on, Jay. I bought all the altcoins with
you last bull market, but it was a
disaster. Remember you bought 500 to
2500 worth every live stream?" Oh, I
remember. I remember. Yep. I remember.
2022, 2023, I was stacking up and that's
why I haven't bought any now. But let me
just say this, eventually these things
are going to pump. It's going to catch
people off guard. See that the mentality
that people have right now of, man, I
got wrecked so hard last time. I'm not
falling for that again. Is exactly why
it's going to pump this time. Exactly
why it's going to pump this time. Baby,
Ali Gaming turned 400 to 10K.
You know, the Dunning Krueger effect.
Thank you. Thank you. You you must be
way behind in the stream. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. See, this person
says Cardano is trash. If you think
Cardano is trash, don't buy it. My My
thing with Cardano is I have all the
Cardano I want. I'm holding my Cardano.
I'm not selling it. In fact, me and my
wife opened up our altcoin portfolio
just the other night. He said, "Weesh,
this is bad, man. Can't believe we let
all this go. We had so much money in
there. And now it's it's worth literally
we opened up the dang portfolio and we
got a call. It was a margin call. Just
kidding. But it is not looking good. It
is not looking good. Um
Dark Shield.
Yeah, I forgot about Dark Shield.
Uh Jason 618 or 786. Here's the next
possible rejection.
Are we talking about Bitcoin?
Yeah. So for Bitcoin, the next possible
rejection here is going to be going to
be in my opinion this let's check it out
here.
In my opinion, the next possible
rejection on Bitcoin is going to be
between
I'd say 65 between 653
and 658. So yeah, right around both of
those in my opinion. right around both
of those.
Yeah. But but the daily looks pretty
bullish. I'm not going to lie. The daily
on Bitcoin does look pretty bullish.
And the two week on Bitcoin looks pretty
bullish. I mean, Bitcoin is looking kind
of bullish. What can I say? What can I
say? You know, maybe this is one of
those patterns, guys. The Bitcoin loves
this pattern. Bitcoin loves this
pattern.
This is a classic Bitcoin pattern. Like,
go back to the like uh where's a classic
one of those was right over here.
Right. Right here. We formed this and
then we just actually this isn't a
classic one of those patterns. We formed
this pattern for 25 years actually. But
where I know that like last cycle we had
so many of those patterns. Let's go back
in time here. Oh wait, we have to go to
the daily. Hang on. Yeah, here we go.
Like remember all this? This is what I'm
talking about. We have this and then we
break out. Um where's another good
example?
We had a lot of those right here. Right?
We break out, we form this, and then
whoop.
Bitcoin loves to do that kind of thing.
So, I would not be surprised if we don't
get another big old VO to the upside and
come to the top of the range around
67ish,
right? That would not surprise me in the
slightest.
In the slightest. Do I trade with any
strategy or just instincts and
experiments? Definitely experiments for
sure. What I like to do is I like to
sniff the wind. Which way is the wind
blowing today? You know, and then what I
do is I roll some dice. I roll them.
Boom.
Whatever number that d lands on, lands
on, that's how many figures I put on the
trade, right? If I roll 12 figure trade,
is that a billion dollars? I don't know.
Too dumb. I'm too dumb to know. Um,
too dumb to know. But honestly, strategy
that's for losers. You know what I'm
saying? Really, it's all about just how
do you feel that day? You know, wake up
in the morning, how am I feeling that
day? Feeling bullish?
You know, would your instincts ever be
wrong? Could my instincts ever be wrong?
No, I'm just joking. If you want to know
all about my trading strategies, go and
watch my free course, 18 sessions.
18 sessions. My strategy is basically I
long support and I short resistance
and I look for some kind of confirmation
to get into the trade on some kind of
indicator. That's literally my strategy.
So, for example, this morning, the trade
that was taken live in the VIP community
from this back test here, the reason why
I took this trade here is because we
came down and we made a nice low
earlier today, right? We had liquidity
right here. Well, first of all, the
trading plan this morning was this.
Okay, the the because because when I do
a live stream in the VIP, I come up with
a plan for the day, right? We come to
the chart and we plan our the potential
trades we would want to take. The first
trading plan I gave this morning was to
come down to this level here. What
happened in the moment however was
instead of coming down to my level we
front run the level but we took out
these stop losses. So, we got a stop
hunt, right? And as we got the stop
hunt, we saw a very, very bullish
divergence forming here, which made me
say because we have such a bullish
divergence here and we front run the
level, if we come back down to back test
the golden pocket, I'm going to I'm
going to have to go for the long trade.
And we did. We came we backed down, we
back tested the Fibonacci golden pocket
right here. And so, when I saw we were
taking a bounce, that's where I took the
long trade. Right?
So that was a strategy but it was
modified in the moment. The the the
original plan the original strategy
right here was to come down to this area
and bounce from here with bullish
divergences, right? But because we
bounced from here with bullish
divergences and front ran the level and
we bounced from the PC plus liquidity
grab, I modified that to get in on a
back test. Same deal with planning for
the short trade from this area today.
It's funny because today the only short
trade that's not true. Well, you could
have shorted earlier this morning and
had a really nice short, but ever since
I came to the chart this morning, the
only short you actually could have taken
and made money on was the one from right
here, the setup given right here. And to
be fair, we didn't necessarily have the
confirmations for that move. But
nonetheless, because it was a key level
of resistance, we still ended up with a
pretty decent rejection from there on
the first tap of that 786. It came down
about 0.5% which by the way for a scalp
trade is excellent.
Excellent.
You know I think I
where did I where did I hit my first TP1
on on the long trade [music] was
I guess I guess it was around uh around
around that around a 6%.
So yeah, that's an excellent scout.
What time do I host premium live? I
personally do it every Monday and
Wednesday at 9:00 in the morning Eastern
time. But we have we have four
instructors in the Casper crew [music]
and we do every New York open, every
London open, every Asia open, and then
randomly, not randomly, it's on a
schedule. One of the instructors is an
altcoin stream. And we cover way more
assets than just Bitcoin,
you know. Um,
but yeah, Trump talks around 4.
Interesting. Interesting.
Okay. I wonder what he's going to say.
What's Donald Trump going to say? I
better get my hair ready for Donald
Trump cuz this is unacceptable when the
president speaks. I got to fix this.
There we go.
actually. There we go.
Can we look at Crow? Can we look at
Crow?
Yeah. I don't see why we can't look at
Crow.
We could take a look at Crow.
Wait, this can't be right.
Is this really the asset we're looking
at here? Kronos, right?
Kronos means time in Greek.
Kronos in Greek means time. That's where
we get our English word chronology.
Chronology comes from Kronos.
Kronos.
Yeah, that's it. Wow,
man. I don't have enough Kronos for this
stuff, man.
Well, what do I think about it? I I I I
I I I [laughter]
Well, we're getting an oversold wave on
the monthly. That's all I can say, which
we've never really had before. This
thing is beat down from its beginning to
list on Coinbase back in 2021.
It is down 94%.
Look, I don't know anything about
Kronos.
I'll be [music] honest with you. Is this
cryptocrow.com?
What is Crow?
Let's Google it here.
What is this crypto? Yeah, it's
crypto.com.
All right. It's it's the uh it's the
native cryptocurrency of the Kronos
chain and the ecosystem powering
crypto.com.
All right. So,
all I can say is this. based on the
chart itself. I I I I
can't know anything about the
fundamentals of this thing based on the
chart itself. But all I can say is if
this is actually a legitimate
good project that has a real use case
that will be used in the future, you're
buying it at a cheap price. You're
buying at 94% discount. And when it
comes to things like this, you have to
do your own fundamental research. But
the upside is almost 2,000%.
And assuming we don't make a lower low,
the downside is 10%.
All right. So, so that gives us a
risk-to-reward ratio.
Assuming we make a new all-time high or
at least come to the previous alltime
high. I'm not saying we're going to. I'm
just analyzing this as a risk-to-reward
ratio. All right. The risk-to-reward
ratio is this.
The downside potential is 10%. The
upside potential is 2,000%. This is
giving us a 129 times more potential
reward than potential risk. 120 times
more potential upside than downside. So
if you based on your own fundamental
research of Kronos and Crypto.com feel
like it's a solid project, then you're
buying at a very good price. All right?
You're buying at a very good price.
You're buying at historic support. This
has been support since November 2022.
It's been held once, twice, three times
as support.
And of course, I'm pretty sure we
rejected from the Let's go ahead and put
this on uh
log scale fib here. Yeah, we rejected
from the golden pocket
last time, last bull market, right?
That's all I can say because I don't
know anything about the fundamentals of
Kronos. I just know that Greek in Greek
Kronos means time. All right? All right.
And that's where we get our our English
word chronology. Chronological order.
That's all I know. [music] You know,
that's all I know.
You know,
um
5 minute the 100 about to cross the 200
on Bitcoin. Let's pump, baby. Shout out
to memory man in the chat. What's going
on, bro?
What is going on? Crow burned and
unburned a bunch of coins while ago. It
was funny. Is that how that happened?
How old am I?
In three days, I will cross the line
from youth
into
old. All right. In three days, I'm about
to officially become
old. Old old. An old man. The beard is
not even fully grown in yet, but it's
already about to turn gray. in 3 days.
The hair
still pretty good, but only 3 days away
until my hairline recedes by at least 17
in.
That's how old I am. All right.
Crazy. Crazy.
Today, I drive a Ram 1500. In 3 days,
I'm going to be driving a minivan.
All right. Today, I have six-pack abs.
in 3 days. Beer gut. It's crazy. I'm
that close to being old. Never thought
it would happen to me. When you're
young, you feel like you'll never be
old. And then one day, you wake up,
boom, you're old.
How did this happen? How How in the
world is Lincoln Park's Hybrid Theory
album
27 years old?
That's so old. That's 30 years old. The
music I grew up with is 30 years old.
Yeah. I mean that this is crazy, man.
That is crazy,
man. Shout out to Feal Matter Machine.
Yes, I'm 25. Yes, I am 25 for sure.
I'm 25.
Um, do I have a video on Fibonacci? Do I
have a video on Fibonacci? [laughter]
Do I ever, man? Oh man, I love
Fibonacci. One of my favorite things to
talk about. Let's see. Do I think I have
a video on Fibonacci? Fibonacci
retracement. How to use Fibonacci
to become a profitable trader. Part 18
of my free trading course.
And not only that, but also if you go to
other playlists here, this day full day
trading guide. All right,
I have a video of Fibonacci. The right
way to draw Fibonacci retracements. The
right way to draw Fibonacci retracements
is right here, guys. All right.
Um, also I have even more than that. I'm
pretty sure if you go to if you go to
the playlist section, guys, on my
YouTube channel, I mean, it's a gold
mine in here. Let's see. Let's see. What
do I have? Crypto trading strategies.
crypto trading strategies. All right.
Uh
I'm pretty sure I have Fibonacci in
here. If not, just watch this playlist
of of my crypto trading strategies,
guys. I have so many videos where I've
gone over so many trades that I've taken
and different strategies,
you know, in this playlist. Honestly, I
mean, look at this thumbnail. This
trading strategy changed everything.
Look at this thumbnail. Wow. I'm
curious. I want to watch this. What?
What?
>> Wow. The best trading strategy for
beginners. Wow. Look at this. Look at
this text on there, too. The editor,
man. The editing on this video is
amazing. I don't even remember doing
that. When did Oh, did I do this? I
might have done this. Wow. Look at this.
Wow. My goodness. Oh my. Wow. Jason
Casper. Wow. Look, this guy must be a
really good trader. He's so happy
because he followed Jason Casper. Wow.
Jason Casper
with the content. Man, I impressed
myself. I impressed myself. Sheesh. How
could you guys sleep on this YouTube
channel? I'm telling you.
All right. Bitcoin's pumping, baby.
Bitcoin is pumping, baby. Here we go. I
even hired an Asian for YouTube. Yes, I
know, man. Seriously.
Yeah, RIP Chester. Seriously, man. That
that you know what? I do not I like I
hate uh how do I say this? I don't
really care usually if like not that I
don't mean to sound heartless, but it's
very strange to me when people get upset
because of celebrities dying, right? I
never understood it until Chester from
Lincoln Park died. That that affected
me. That actually did affect me. That
was pretty crazy, actually. Then I
understood. Then I understood
who edited that video. I you know what?
I think it might have been me. I I think
back in that time I was experimenting
with maybe trying to get some more views
or something. When did this video come
out? Let's see. 3 years ago
on March 1st, 2023. Okay. So, this was
Yeah, I was I was really experimenting
because we had just come out of the bare
market. The channel was dying dying.
Not as bad as it is now, actually. Now
my channel is literally right now is the
worst in history of Jason Casper is
right now. But at the time back then my
channel was dying and I was like what
can I do to revive the channel? I
thought you know what I must hire an
Asian guy to celebrate his his trading
wins,
you know, and that's exactly what I did.
And look, honestly,
I think I had like 80,000 subs back
then. And now I'm at 160. I doubled my
subs. All I had to do was hire an Asian.
Isn't that amazing? Pro tip for all you
aspiring YouTubers out there. A pro tip.
Your channel's dying.
Pro tip, baby.
Hump song. If it breaks 55 65, how did
it affect me? Well, [music]
honestly,
he Lincoln Park was a very influential
band in my life. So, it was just a
strange thing. Just it was very I I
don't know. It was a strange thing. It
was It was just a strange feeling. It
was the first time a famous person died.
It made me feel something. All right. I
can't explain it. I can't explain it.
All right.
Would
you hire an Asian for your trades?
Well, if they're Korean, probably. Cuz
those Koreans are insane at trading.
Do women like Fibonacci?
Um, I don't know. I have to ask my wife.
Um, the world ended in 2012. Today, more
people own smartphones and toothbrushes.
That is crazy. Time is accelerating,
says someone.
It does feel that way. It really does
feel that way. Um,
shout out to uh, make me a million. He
says, "Get VIP 7 fees signing up Bitbase
with the link in the description. Very,
very, very low fees." That's true, guys.
Bitbase, very, very, very low fees. Uh,
you get VIP level seven fees on uh, on
this. How do I see my fees here? I don't
know how to see my fees.
Oh, here we go. Fees. Okay. Okay. Yeah.
VIP level 7. I don't know if you guys
can see that. Can you guys see that? Let
me zoom in on it.
Fees VIP level 7 is going to give you,
if you sign up using my link, 0.005
maker, 0.02 taker. All right. Now, not
only that, but again, if you sign up,
you get we're we're giving away $500 a
week, guys. If you sign up to Blowin,
all right, Blowoffin is giving you
$2,000 a week and also 0% limit order.
0.02% market order. All right, very low
fees for both these exchanges and
giveaways. But today is the day that
we're giving away $500 currency of
Bitbase. All right, Bitbase. Why
Bitbase? Well, because think about it,
Bybit and Coinbase, two of the best
exchange in the world. Imagine if they
got married together and had a baby.
Imagine if Bitbase and I'm sorry, Bybit
and Coinbase got together and made a
baby with Jason Casper. What would that
equal? That would equal a weekly $500
giveaway.
All right. If Bitbase and Jason Casper
had a baby, it equals $500 giveaway. If
Coinbase and Bybit had a baby, it equals
Bitbase. All right. So, I'm having a
baby with Coinbase and Bybit's baby. And
this is the offspring right here. Look
at that. They always told me that Bit
Base and Jason Casper would make
beautiful babies. They say they would
have the most exotic looking eyes. And
boy were they right. The heterocchromia
is intense. Look at those lips. What the
heck? Looks like I've been out in the
cold for 25 years playing a trumpet
without any chapstick. I've been out in
the cold for 25 years playing a trumpet
without any chapstick.
You know, we're giving away $500
today.
You know,
[music]
Yeah, [music] it's so criminal. The
market maker sending messages
subliminal.
It's so double timal. [music]
Going up like the chimney for criminal.
Yeah, Jason Casper, not a criminal.
[music]
Giving you the messages, they so
subliminal. Get your chin over the bar.
The chiminal outside, but we're [music]
here in the terminal. The take off the
rocket blast going so fast. The Bitcoin
price is about to [singing] go past.
Just a blast. All the people end last.
[music]
You know we're in first. You know we do
it fast. We got the green in [music] the
trees. I'm right here, baby. Listen to
me. We about to pump up the shorts. We
both squeeze. And then we go in the
kitchen. We eat the cheese. We take the
cheese. I [music] love the raw cheddar.
Maybe Kobe Jack. It tastes better. I put
it on the bread in the microwave. The
Bitcoin price. [music] It comes in
waves. It goes up. It goes down. It
[singing] goes left. It goes right. The
bears in the bulls. They're in a fight.
Don't you know it lasts all night. Asia
open. They do it right. They pump and
they dump. [music] It's a big battle.
Camala versus Trump. They're in the
saddle. We're out here like my name is
[music] Sat. We gamble away our dad's
money. Fat. Fat. For real. [music] We
got the feels. Jason Casper. He's
slipping on banana peels like we're
going around in Mario Kart. Is Jason
Casper Spark? Heck no. [music] He's a
[__] Uh
yeah.
Uh
here we go. We got a green candle, baby.
[music] Uh we got a green candle about
to pump up. Here we go. I got the coffee
in the cup. J Casper on the treadmill.
[music] Your boy acting tough. But let
me know if you had enough. Big shout to
Wendy Core in the chat. No, the beat's
over. Uh, no it's not [music] in the
chat. Will you pee in the bushes today
about that? Hey, I don't Now the beat's
really over. Man, that what a strange
beat that was, honestly. [snorts]
Sheesh. Um,
man, we have some emotional beats today,
though. This is getting me emotional
right now.
They need to do a giveaway every stream.
500 is nothing to them.
That's true. exchanges. If you really
want to make money, it's all about the
exchanges.
About the exchanges. [snorts] Uh yeah.
[music]
Yeah.
The real money,
it's all about the exchanges. Uh hey yo
[music] hey yo.
If you want to make the real money,
baby, it's all about exchanges. make
[music] so much more than trading
ranges. But I don't see any changes
outside. [music] All I see are the
strangers cuz I don't see anybody I
know. So sit back and listen to the
Jason Casper crypto flow and welcome to
the Jason Casper show. Where [music] do
we begin? [singing] I'll let you know.
Uh we long to top high leverage and it
starts to drop. [music]
So scared my heart nearly stops. We were
pumping but now we stop cuz the market
maker drop it down. They make a
[music and singing] clown out of me on
the internet around town. They say Jay
we won't let you win. We'll make a fool
of you. [music] We will begin to
liquidate your assets
straight to zero. You ain't no hero to
back [music] test
the market cipher B. You know it makes
delirio [singing]
assets.
Jay Casper. Uh, [music] you know, I
never back test. I don't trade with a
strategy that's not best. Uh, how do I
trade? You want to know? [music] I wake
up and I listen to the flow of the way I
feel. Am I long? Am I short? [music]
I don't know. [singing] I won't get
[__] cuz I'm so smart. I can outsmart
the market. [music] Profits, don't you
know? They will start it into my wallet.
I'm making the money. J Casher on the
treadmill. Not [music and singing] so
funny. But then boom, liquidated in an
instant and I can't even hit this. How
will [music] I tell my wife on Christmas
I lost all the money that I wanted to
piss this to kiss this the mistletoe
under the tree. Jason Casper lost
everything. [music] But hey, I'll get it
back one day. 100x from the top. That's
the way. When you lose a trade, just
double down. [music]
Okay,
man.
I don't know. Let's Let's actually check
the order flow right now. Let's check
the order flow right now.
Um,
why long if everyone knows it's going to
39K? Look, we long, we short. [music]
It is what it is, man. All right, we
longed from the golden pocket back test.
So, let's see what happens here.
Um, just honestly kind of like a little
lack of participation up here, but we
did have wow 223 million longs long
here. We have a volume divergence big
time here. It's just lack of
participation. We don't have enough
buyers stepping in to sustain this move
to the upside. So, maybe we do get a
little bit of a consolidation from here.
You know, we are at a daily level. We
are at a single print. Maybe we
consolidate here for just a smidgen.
[music]
All right. Maybe we consolidate here for
just a smidgey own. All right.
So, let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
Let's see. Let's see.
What do I think about lit token? I never
heard of it to be honest.
What's the name of the orderflow
website? It's called Market Monkey
Terminal, MMT. And honestly, it's a
pretty it's it's an amazing platform.
And I think they do have a free version,
but I have the paid version. I've got
the ultra version, but honestly,
uh I don't even know if I need the the
paid version. I just always have the
paid version of everything cuz give me
the best, baby. That's that's my
mentality. Give me the dang best. All
right.
Um [music]
39K. Shout out to DB88. Um, yeah. So,
look, honestly, you know, look, I'm
going to say the same thing I've been
saying forever, which is this. The time
and price target for this cycle is 39K.
Let's see. Let's see if it's going to
happen. It's It's going to happen by
October, you know. So, let's see. I'm
hoping for that one more catastrophic
move to the downside, you know. Hoping
for it. I wonder how many steps I've
gotten today. Let's check out how many
steps have I gotten today.
Um
19,000. Not so bad. 19,000.
19,000 steps, baby. That's not so bad.
45K for you. Yeah, Market Monkey
Terminal really is the best, honestly.
Um,
20,000 step. How many steps do you guys
have? You know what? Pretty soon we got
to do our our our Bitbase giveaway.
But before we do our giveaway, let me
know how many steps you guys have today.
How many calories do I eat in a day?
I'll give you my weekly average. It's
over 5,000. Over 5,000 calories a day
right now.
Yeah. Last 7 days, 5,189 calorie
average. The week before that, 5,156.
The week before that, 5,286.
Week before that, only 4,733.
I'm usually around 5,000 calories a day.
Honestly, I I feel the best around 5,000
calories a day. That's the way to go.
And I have been maintaining my weight on
5,000 calories a day since
June. So, I have [music] pretty much
maintained my weight on 5,000 calories a
day for about 8 weeks, which is a nice
place to be. And I'm trying to push the
food up a little bit here. I'm gonna I'm
trying I'm going to be trying to push
the food up a little bit and see if I
can't put on a little bit of actual
muscle. See what I could do, honestly.
Let's see.
You did four miles on the stream. Oh,
you know what? We need an egg code.
We need an egg code. You're losing
muscle in the gym instead of gaining.
What the heck? Here's what you got to
do. All right. Here's what you got to
do. First of all, if you're actually
training and you're losing muscle,
there's two things you got to look at.
Thing number one is your training. All
right? Are you training? How what are
you training? Like I recommend
if you've been you've been training for
at least a year, you've been lifting
weights for at least a year, I recommend
you switch to a more
lower volume, higher intensity model.
All right? Maybe like an upper lower
four days a week or honestly push pull
legs three days a week only or full body
two days a week
and focus on maybe like
very few exercises one two to three sets
each hard sets right if you're just in
there fluffing and pumping it's not
going to do anything but the second
variable is your diet you know if You're
losing weight while you're working out.
It means you're not eating enough.
Honestly,
means you're not eating enough.
Um, what were we going to do?
What were we going to do?
I eat for two people. Yeah. How do I eat
5,000 calories? That's just my body
likes to eat a lot of food. So, yeah. I
don't I don't know how people don't eat
so much. I honestly don't know how
people don't eat so much. Like for me,
like if I sit down for a meal, I usually
eat three meals a day. Two big meals and
a small meal.
It's usually ends up being two 2,000
calorie meals and one 1,000 calorie
meal. And I don't feel full. I don't
feel like I don't feel full or anything
after that. I just feel normal, you
know? So, I don't know how people eat so
little. I don't know how people eat so
little. I just have a strange strange
body. Very inefficient, right? If I was
a car, I'd get like 3 miles to the
gallon.
What do I think about working out with a
busted back?
You got the spine juice squeeze out. I
don't know cuz I am not a doctor. But I
would say this. I feel like in most
instances, doing nothing is worse than
doing something. Obviously, if a busted
back, you shouldn't be squatting and
deadlifting with with a barbell.
But I mean, I think like the body can
kind of heal itself and especially if
you're getting blood flow to that area.
So, if I had a busted back, I'd probably
be doing like whatever I could do to get
blood flow to that area. Obviously, as
light or as heavy as as possible, but
I'm not a doctor. I'm not a physical
therapist. I would hire a physical
therapist.
All right? I actually work with a
physical therapist
um because I myself have some back
issues, right? And I've had a lot of
success
fixing like really bad back pain just by
working with a physical therapist. Now,
if there's an actual disc issue, I don't
know how much you can fix that, but I I
don't know really what to say, honestly.
Um,
you're not eating enough. How should you
eat more? I mean, it's so easy,
literally. I mean, well, here's what you
have to really do.
If you're losing weight, add in a little
bit of extra food every day until your
weight stays the same. All right? So, if
you're losing weight consistently, every
single day, take a dang shot of olive
oil. Extra virgin olive oil,
uh the the you know, the first
coldressed extra virgin olive oil, like
the high quality, full of polyphenols
and like healthy fats and all that
stuff. Not only is it healthy for you,
but it's an easy. You take a shot of
olive oil, that's an easy 200 calories
in a shot, right? Boom. [music] Or put
that on your dang salad or dip your
bread in it or whatever.
Put it on your oats. I put olive oil on
my yogurt
until you get to the place where your
weight's consistent for like 2 weeks.
Then you know, all right, this is how
much I need to eat to maintain our
weight. Then just push it up a little
bit from there. Just push it up a little
bit from there,
you know. All right, the egg code. Thank
you, man. The egg code. Thank you. Thank
you. Shout out to Make Me Millie. Shout
out to Sud.
What exercises should you do?
Uh, well, I'm a big fan of
just normal good oldfashioned
exercises. So, for back,
[music] weighted pull-ups, weighted
chin-ups,
uh, barbell rows, shrugs,
you know. um and variations of those. If
you can do a cable row or a chest
supported row, excellent. Chest
supported rows on a bench with
dumbbells. Excellent.
Basically, for your back, you want to
make sure you're hitting your lats.
That's going to be a vertical pull. You
want to hit your rhomboids and your
lower traps. That's going to be like a
horizontal pull. You want to hit your
upper traps. It's going to be a shrug.
All right.
for chest and shoulders, dips,
push-ups,
and got your lat and incline presses,
dumbbell and barbell.
I mean, what do I know? I mean,
honestly, you should ask Make me a
Millie how to get those lats.
Honestly, you should ask him what to do.
What do you do, Make Me a Millie?
Sh make me a millie.
What do you do to get those lats, bro?
And that back. How do you get such
developed back?
Um, all right. The egg code today is
back. B A C because we want to know how
make me a millia gets that gets that
wide Vtaper, you know.
Um,
look at Make me a Millie. Look at this.
Sheesh, bro. That is That's as far as I
can zoom in. My goodness. Look at that
Vtaper. We should ask Make me a Millie,
honestly, what he does for his back.
Whatever he does, that's what that's
what we should all do. All right. Which
is not even true, by the way, cuz
everyone's different. That's another
thing. Everyone's different. So, an
exercise might it might work for you,
might not work for someone else,
honestly.
for me. And I don't have the I don't
have a back like Make Me a Million, but
it's been the weighted chin-ups,
the horizontal rows,
and the shrugs.
Then, of course, like uh shoulder press,
standing, seated shoulder presses. Um,
and I never train legs, so don't even
worry about it. No, I'm joking.
Got to do squats. Squats and deadlifts.
Really? Squats and deadlifts and
variations of those. So, Romanian
split squats, I'm sorry, Bulgarian split
squats, Romanian deadlifts,
um, you know, lunges, weighted lunges,
belt squats are great, leg presses are
great, front squats are really good for
working your quads. But honestly,
my quads, the way I built them the best
is with a Smith machine Bulgarian split
squat or dumbbell Bulgarian split squat.
>> I can't comment on on calves because I I
can't grow my calves no matter what.
Shout out to New Earth Guardian. Shout
out to Yeshua Hamashiach.
Yeah, I know. Shout out to Jose.
>> Those three [snorts] exercises are
linear work for everyone. Yeah.
>> Yeah, those three exercises.
I'm from Romanian deadlift. That's
what's up. That's what's up.
High barbell back squats and hack squat.
Yo. Oh, yeah. The hack squat is great if
you have access to that.
I don't have a hack squat. I have a
Smith machine. I can do Smith machine
hack squats. [music]
But yeah, the hack squat that'll really
isolate those quads.
If I if I was going to a commercial gym,
I would definitely I used to do a lot of
hack squats and now I see people doing
these pendulum squats on the internet.
I've never seen a pendulum squat machine
in my life, but it seems like the best
it seems like literally the best leg
exercise that a tall person can do. cuz
I've spent a lot of time working on my
barbell back squat.
Um,
and I've I've spent a lot of time on my
technique and my range of motion on the
barbell back squat and it did not grow
my legs
as much as I wanted it to. You know, I
know. I need Frankie Candle Cavs. I need
Frankie Candle Cavs.
Jojo Productions lost 27 lbs walking in
the past 2.5 months. That's what's up,
bro. Congratulations. Congratulations.
Yeah. Every time I think about getting a
commercial gym membership, I think to
myself, the nearest commercial gym to me
is probably about 40 minutes away, which
means almost an hour and a half of
driving.
And then I just can't bring myself to
drive to the gym when I literally have a
gym like right through this door behind
me here. Like my gym is through this
door right here. There's the gym door
right behind me. It's open.
I call it IHOG. The IHOG gym. The
international house of gains, baby.
You know,
it's called the IMOG gym.
The best squat I've ever [laughter] done
is when I found $100. Can you imagine
someone finds $100, they literally squat
down to get it instead of just bend
over? That'd be so funny.
You got a little fat and your calves
exploded. Well, Caesar, here's the
thing. I used to be very fat and I still
had skinny calves.
I was very fat and I still skinny cat. I
I'm I was the most unflattering type of
fat. Like there's the kind of fat guy
who has like a big gut, but he has like
such a solid like lower body. It doesn't
look so bad cuz he's stocky, you know?
He looks strong and stocky.
You know, massive calves, massive
glutes, massive thighs,
you know, very compact, small waist.
Even though he has a gut to the side,
he's got a big gut, but from the front
and from the back, he still has a
Vtaper.
That's not the kind of fat I am. All
right. The kind of fat I am is
stomach and chest fat like this. Legs
like this, arms like this. All right.
Neck like this. All right. Massive
double chin like this.
All right. And then my my face like
this. That's kind of fat. I'm just all
chin and man boobs and and and gut and
love handles,
skinny calves, skinny legs. I have like
a cortisol. I'm like a I don't know. I
look like I look like like just Yeah,
it's just that that's how I was, man.
So, doesn't work for me. You know what
I'm saying? Doesn't work for me.
I just didn't get I didn't get that I
didn't get those genetics. You know what
I'm saying? I didn't get the fat calf
genetics.
You know what I'm saying?
Anatoli videos.
I'd like those, too.
Shout out to Anatoli.
Yeah, you're right. Make me a millie.
You're right. And I've thought that,
too. Like, I thought, you know, I don't
have to go every workout. I could go
once a week. Here's the problem. I'm
such a homebody that I I would just
imagine that if I had the gym
membership, I wouldn't even go once a
week. But maybe I'll get it.
Maybe I will. There's a really nice gym
like 40 minutes away from me. It's like
an old school gym.
It's like a stuck in the stuck in the
late 90s gym. It has all the old school
hammer strength plate loaded machines.
It just has that vibe of the old old
school gym from the late '9s, early
2000s. You go in, there's like the big
signs on the ceiling hanging down on
chains. I say like arms, legs, back,
chest, so so you know where to work out
each thing.
So, I was thinking about going to that
gym, you know,
photo of the Fatty Jay. I do have some
photos of the Fatty Jay.
You got to remember this is a long time
ago.
Um,
all right. Bitcoin trying to get the
pump here, baby. Trying to get the pump.
You know [music] what I mean? We're
trying to get the pump.
See,
I'm hoping for a big move, but
you can inject growth hormone right into
the calves.
Why did I short if I believe we're going
higher? I've been in this short for a
long time. Okay, I've been holding this
short for quite some time. this short.
I've been holding it since
uh July 30th. Okay,
July 30th. So, I've been in the short
for a long time. Uh why am I short?
Because it's a hedge. It's a zerorisk
trade right now. If I get stopped out,
it will lose $4,000 of the 3,000,
right? So, it's literally going to be a
$100 potential. I'm risking $100 with my
stop loss above these highs.
I'm in a over $600,000 worth of longs.
All right, close to 700K worth of longs,
which if the might get stopped out of
here, this trade will be up like 30
grand. This trade here will be up,
I don't know, 10 grand. So, I'm going to
be up 40 grand.
Sorry, $39,900
net profit. That's why I'm in the short
because what if we dump from here? It is
resistance.
Then if we dump from here, I literally
have unrealized,
you know, unrealized profit on the line
right now. Close to close to 30 grand,
[music]
right? So, by holding a short, I'm
risking $100. By not holding a short,
I'm risking 30 grand. Do you see how
that that is like the reality of this
situation? Unrealized profit is just
that. It's unrealized.
It's unrealized. So, if I'm not short
and we dump down, I'm 30 grand could go
down the toilet. If we pump and I'm
short, I'm literally going to lose a h
100red bucks. It's a good deal. It's a
good deal. We need to do our bitbased
giveaway.
All right.
We need to do our Bitbase giveaway,
guys. What I need you to do
is spam the chat with your Bitbase
user ID.
Span the chat with your Bitbase
user ID. We're going to
Here we go. We're going to count down
from 10 and highlight somebody.
Here we go. All right. 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3
2 one. Boom. All right, let's see who
our winner is here. All right, our
winner is
um
Ma Yez. All right. Mama Yez.
Mama Yez. Let's see if
I can find that.
If I can find that screenshot that I
just took. I know you guys can see
everything. That's okay.
Ah, where is that screenshot?
No, that's not it. That's not it.
It's not it. [music]
It's not it either.
Where is that screenshot? Dang it. Dang
it.
>> [music]
>> My computer is is doing something new
these days, guys, where I can't pull a
screenshot onto my dang.
All right, we're going to have to do
another another another countdown, I
guess, cuz
I can find them.
[music]
I can't. All right. All right. We're
going to do another countdown. All
right. We're gonna do another countdown.
All right. Spam your dang thing again.
>> Um.
All right. This time I'm going to try
and get it to save on my desktop. All
right. Here we go. Here we go. Here we
go. All right.
5 4 3 2 1 boom. All right, let's see who
the winner is this time. All right, this
time the winner is Sudep. Shout out to
Sudep. All right, Sudep is the winner.
Let's see if I can drag this over
here.
I have to figure out how to fix my
computer.
So, [music]
when I take a screenshot on my Mac,
maybe some of you guys know this, it
used to go to my desktop,
but shout out to Sudep.
Yeah, Sudep's our winner.
It used to go to my desktop, now it
doesn't.
All right, Sudep, I'm going to send it
over to Bitbase.
>> [music]
>> All right.
Yeah, I have to figure out how to fix
that in my Mac. I'm going to have to AI
it, you know. [music] I'm going to have
to AI it. figure out how to fix that.
I see you here. Mama YZ,
I see you, bro.
Um,
all right. M Al mom alunz,
here's what I'll do, bro. Here's what
I'll do. Because I'm a nice guy. Because
I'm a nice guy.
Um,
I wish there was a way to see your
original.
You know what? There's nothing to do.
There's nothing to do. I wish I wish I
could say, "Send me your address and
I'll send you $500." But I can't because
scammers will fake it.
And then we'll have a thousand tickets
open in Discord. Everyone claiming I'm
Mama Unz. I'm the winner. There's
nothing to do. I'm sorry, bro. It is
what it is. It's random.
It is what it is. It's random, man. It's
like the time I almost won the lottery,
but I lost it by one number. All right.
Next time. Next time, bro.
Next time, bro. All right.
Next time. Sign up for the blowof fin
$2,000 giveaway. All right, every week
we're giving away four $500 prizes. It's
through the Discord, through the free
Discord.
So, go check it out. Go try it out. Go
try it out for yourself and see if it
fits.
All right.
Here's the thing, mama. I don't know
what your user ID is anymore, bro. I
don't know what your user ID is anymore.
I could check after the stream, but
right now the farthest back I can go on
my YouTube stream isn't actually going
to show me your user ID. Sadly, it's not
going to show it to me. Shout out to our
super chat, Dennis Marv. He said, "Could
you please put these in order of
significance? Market structure, volume,
volume, profile, cipher v, trend line."
Shout out to Dennis Mar for the super
chat. Thank you so much for the super
chat.
Um
okay in order of importance definitely
uh market structure is number one
because that is the basis for every
single trade you take. Every trade you
take you're taking it because you think
we're either bottoming out and reversing
a trend or continuing a trend. The
second is going to be volume profile
because you should always be looking to
buy at a discount and sell at a premium
and avoid buying and selling at at fair
fair range, fair trade, fair price. Um
then on after that I would say
trend lines because trend lines act as
support or resistance. Uh and then the
last and final thing is market cipher B
because really for me market cipher B is
telling me if the price is coming to a
a zone of interest do I have a reason to
pull the trigger you know do I have a
reason to pull the trigger.
All right. Shout out to Ali Gaming Tube
HD. Shout out to T1M3ATK.
Doesn't crypto and Bitcoin need to
generate opportunity for people to sell
out of stocks.
Yeah, I guess so. I mean,
I don't know if Mo I I can't imagine
that most people go in and out of stocks
and crypto like that, but I'm pretty
sure big money is well diversified.
And right now, compared to stocks,
at least compared to the dang S&P 500,
Bitcoin's way low at a way better
opportunity right now,
you know,
is there an exchange I can recommend?
Honestly, you should never trade without
a VPN, bro. Um,
you should never trade without a VPN in
general. Um,
yeah, I don't know. I can't recommend an
exchange that's not Antarctic or Blofin
or Bitbase. I mean, those are the ones
that should not have KYC or VPN
requirements [music]
and Antarctics is a DEX,
you know.
Shout out to Dennis Marv.
Guys, here's the thing. The whole
giveaway thing is final. It is what it
is, guys. It is what it is. I'm sorry if
if that upsets anybody. It is what it
is.
>> [music]
>> We do we give away literally thousands
of dollars
every single month on this channel. So
there will be plenty of opportunity. All
right. There was a mistake that
happened. It was on my end. But that's
just part of the randomness of it.
That's part of the randomness of it. All
right. It is what it is, guys. I'm
sorry. It is what it is.
Speak no more of this matter. Speak no
more of this matter.
It is what it is. I'm sorry. It is what
it is.
Loin blocks United States IPs now. Hm.
Is that true? Doesn't block mine. I'm
I'm located here in the United States of
America.
The good oldfashioned USA.
the good oldfashioned USA.
[music]
All right. So, shout out to Sue Deep MM.
Life is but a dream.
We're going to get that $500 to ASAP.
Bitcoin to 35K. Ha. I mean, I don't know
if 35K, but
maybe 39, but um
yeah. Yep. The oldfashioned USA. I don't
live in the new fashion USA. I live in
the oldfashioned USA. There's a big
difference between the old and the new
fashion USA's. Guys,
what's my target for this move?
Honestly, why not the mid70s get you?
Why not the mid70s? Why not actually
break out? You know, treadmill just
turned off. You know what that means? It
actually is time to go pee in the
bushes.
It actually is time to go pee in the
bushes, y'all.
Short for the win.
Here's the thing. I don't have a I don't
necessarily have Well, that's not true.
There is a short entry right now, but it
doesn't look the best. Here's the thing.
Here's how I'm playing this. In all
honesty, I'm not I'm I'm longing and
shorting [music] and I don't care about
whether or not the bottom is in for
Bitcoin as far as spot goes.
I am simply looking to buy if we dip
lower.
You know,
this potential move has the potential to
take us up to the value area high of the
range, which is going to be around
$74,000.
Um, but at least first we're going to go
to 67, which is only a 3,000 a $2,500
move from here. You know, it's nothing
too crazy. Nothing too crazy.
Now, I do know this. I have a feeling as
far as blofening goes, I do [music]
someone says someone brought up the
garden state. If you're talking about
New Jersey, I do remember going to New
Jersey and having an issue with the VPN
being required. So maybe that maybe that
is the case for Blofin. [music]
You know,
it's so weird when my my laptop goes
outside, it gets overheated,
starts to blow up.
If I was long at 642 only, would I head
short now?
Um 642, would I head short now? Um
[music]
I don't I don't know actually. Probably
not. I usually don't head It depends. If
I'm scalping for the day, then yeah,
probably.
But it's a difficult question to answer.
It really depends on the situation I was
in. Hedge short, meaning what? If I was
scalping, I could have taken a scalp
short from here and locked in a profit
and had my stop loss
uh above just to keep the position open.
That's probably how I would do it.
Have I heard of people getting having
trouble getting money off KSEX? I have.
And everyone who had an issue with that
in my community has had it resolved
because I reached out to KEX myself and
I said, "Come on, KEX.
and they helped everyone out.
Do I use a DEX or a SEX? I use both. I
I'm open positions on both right now.
This is a decentralized exchange right
here. This is a DEX.
And then this here is a sex.
You're swing short on Bitcoin now. Why
now? Like, let's be honest. You know, I
I don't want to dissuade anyone from
their planning, but the way I'm looking
at Bitcoin now is this. Look at the
daily. The daily looks so bullish. Oh my
goodness. [music] Swing short. I would
never swing short this. How in the world
could you swing short with a bullish
daily? I don't mean to dissuade anybody,
but not only that, we're above the PC of
the range
and it does it not look like this is
about to squeeze like all this liquidity
and come back to the top.
I mean, again, I don't mean to dissuade
anybody, but why are you swinging short
on Bitcoin as we're reclaiming major
support with a bullish confirmation?
Again, I look, I you follow your own
plan, please. You know, cuz come back
tomorrow and we're dumped all the way
down to 25,000. Be like, Jason, why why
did you say not to swing short? Okay, I
was wrong, but it just doesn't look that
bearish to me. You know,
tomorrow stocks will be red.
Taco is live now.
What is taco?
I I do think Bitcoin can get more move
to the upside. This looks like she's
ready to get a big blast off here.
I think I think we're finally breaking
out of this channel thing. I think we're
finally breaking this trend line here.
Taco is Trump. Why is Taco Trump? What
happened?
Are we James winning? Oh yeah,
liquidated. Hey guys, I have to be
honest,
okay? I know I'm a homesteader. All
right, I know I grow my own food, okay?
But if you don't have time, if you don't
have time to bake potatoes, all right,
this is a game changer. If you have to
eat on the road, all right, you want to
eat healthy on the road,
these things. All right,
the Snackyard organic
soft and chewy sweet potato sticks.
They're vegan. And not only are they
vegan, the only ingredient is organic
sweet potato. That's it. They're just
dried sweet potatoes. [music] and
they're really chewy and good. And so
I eat the same thing every day. And I I
eat so many potatoes and sweet potatoes,
but it's a pain to bake them. And if you
don't have them, you have to bake them.
It takes like two hours and then they
have to cool off if you want to take
them somewhere, [music] right? So I
found these things. It's like if I have
to go somewhere cuz I travel a lot.
I don't travel a lot at all, but if I
ever have to go somewhere or I have to
be out for the day because I always
bring all my food with me. This is a
game changer right here, guys. This is a
game changer. One pack is about 240
calories worth of potato. That's a
little bit less than 300 gram. If you
had a raw sweet potato, that's like 280
g of sweet potato. That's like a That's
like a good medium smalish size sweet
potato. You know, you get two two packs
of those. is 480 calories, over 100
carbs, tastes great, just pure sweet
potato. Got the potassium in there. You
know what I'm saying? Trying to get the
potassium.
You know, it's got 500 grams of
milligrams of potassium per bag. You get
1,000 milligrams of potassium.
Only 50 grams of sugar.
Only 50 grams of sugar. What could go
wrong? What could go wrong with 50 grams
of sugar?
I eat like 300 grams of sugar a day.
Isn't that crazy?
Um,
that is pretty crazy.
I hope we get like I'm I'm waiting for
the big pump, guys. I'm I'm waiting for
the big pump here. We're up six grand
right now.
My short stop loss is 65150.
TP on 633.
Okay, I hope it works out for you, man.
Do I see a near brief retracement 1
hour, 4 hour before we go back to 67,
I'm not really seeing that as much here.
And the reason why is because just this
whole just this whole structure to me,
it looks like we consolidated and now
we're breaking out of the consolidation
here, right? I'm not looking at this as
much as a bearish divergence
as much as I'm looking at this as a uh I
know people are looking at this as a
hidden bear dive, but we had bullish
divergence down here. We had bull divs
down here. Bull div right here. And now
we're breaking out the trend line.
Market cyers breaking out the trend
line. Money flow curving back to the
upside. And locally like look at the 24m
minute. Maybe I'm maybe I'm wearing bold
glasses, but this morning when we came
down to this low, we had a very very
bullish divergence right here.
So, I could be wrong, but
you know, I don't necessarily see that
pullback coming, especially after this
chop chop city like this. Man, I I feel
like I feel like we get a bit of a
squeeze here. I I am hoping we get a bit
of a squeeze, you know?
Taco will be speaking at 4:30. Okay,
Bitcoin is pumping now, man.
I'm pretty sure this is a false
breakout, says Stocky.
Um, yeah, but also here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
Let's not forget the context is this.
Okay, the overall context. It's not that
we're breaking out of this channel. It's
that the real breakout, the real fake
out is going to be from up here, right?
This is going to be the real fake out.
So the breakout of this channel is
initiating the bull trap that gets the
fake out from up here. That's how I'm
looking at this. Now look at the daily.
I mean the daily market cy for B is
making me feel like that that push up is
is inevitable and then that could result
in the bull trap, you know, cuz then we
have bearish div on the daily and that
that could be our big move back down.
That's kind of how I'm looking at this
now. You know,
those potatoes are called the snackyard.
the snackyard.
>> Here, let me see if I can I'll get I'll
get a picture for you
and they're good for
I don't know. I don't eat anything
before I work out. So, postworkout. How
about that?
Why don't I draw the value area high and
low of the range since June?
This is the value area low and the high
of the range since June right here. This
is June 2nd right there. So, I'm I'm
going based on the range. This is like
the June range for me. I consider it
right here
since June 3rd is pretty much where I
consider it. June 3rd, we're above most
of the volume. And if we reclaim 67,
that's why I say I think we can go up to
74 because then, you know, once we flip
this guy into support, we're going
straight up to here, you know. And if we
fake out, then we could come back down
to 60K and bounce.
Or we could come all the way back down
and make a new low,
you know. Here we go, baby.
Here we go. Bitcoin.
Here we go. How much are they, Bag? Uh,
they're not cheap. I'll be honest. make
me a millie. It depends on where you get
them. You can buy them in bulk on the
internet, different places,
but in general, they're not very cheap.
They're not very cheap. They're much
It's much cheaper to buy potatoes. It's
much cheaper to grow potatoes. I'm a big
fan of growing my own potatoes.
But honestly, sometimes you're in a
pinch and you need something quick to
go.
That's the way to go. in a pinch.
How's the weather here? The weather here
is pretty nice right now. It's a little
bit sunny out. So sunny that my computer
was overheating.
Uh it's actually a little bit cloudy out
now. I said it's it's partly cloudy.
Partly cloudy. How about that? It's more
Yeah, it's like we got some blue sky.
All right.
We got some blue sky, but the sun just
so happens to be behind a white a big
white puffer. a big white puffer.
Don't look like a short squeeze and
price will go down. All right, we'll see
what happens. Joy and I love you too,
you know. Yeah, it's been raining the
last few days. Yesterday it rained and
then it got real nice. The day before
that, rainy and dreary. Rainy and
dreary.
You know,
anything good for you ain't cheap.
That's not necessarily true. Anything
convenient and good for you is not
cheap. I'd say anything that's
cheap. But dry beans
very cheap. Potatoes are very cheap.
Like but then you got to prepare it all.
Like [music] you know the prep time, the
prep time and time is money.
But and I guess meat is not cheap. There
you go. Meat is not cheap. Eggs are not
cheap. But you get some chickens and
stuff.
But I'll be honest.
No, I don't even know if I should say
that. But yeah, I shouldn't say that.
Healthy convenient food is very
expensive. Healthy convenient food is
extremely expensive. I mean, [music]
I'll tell you, my wife gets these
things. Talk about healthy convenient
food. There's no way this company's
going to stay in business. Let me show
you this.
There's no way that this company's going
to stay in business.
I I mean, who the heck has money to buy
these things? These things are so dang
expensive.
These things, all [music] right, Daily
Harvest. They have pasta bowls. Like,
it's it's gluten-free. All this. It's
literally just all whole food. It's
literally just 100% whole food. There
there's nothing in it. There's no
[music] It's just food. only potatoes,
rice, uh tomato, broccoli, avocado,
uh beans, extra virgin olive oil,
organic like um [music] red pepper, pink
Himalayan pink salt, lime juice,
um tomato paste, lemon juice,
nutritional yeast, organic cumin,
organic paprika, organic oregano,
organic onion powder, and it's it's in a
bowl. It's it's frozen. All it's all
freshly frozen food. like in a bowl. You
just pop it in the oven for a little
bit. But man, those things are
expensive, I'll tell you. And they also
sell these like protein bowls of oatmeal
and it has like fresh produce inside.
It's supposed to stay frozen.
It's just all like whole food. But
there's no way that company's going to
stay in business. There's no way. I told
my wife there's not enough Jason
Casper's wives out there who have the
money for this crap. I mean, let's be
honest.
There's no way that company's going to
stay in business. But I like what
they're doing. I like what they're
doing. It's It's nice to know you can go
to the store and get a TV dinner type
thing that's like lit actually food and
not like a whole bunch of soybean man
tit oil,
you know? Yeah. It's all organic, bro. I
mean organic. You know what I mean? It's
organic. Like it's it's certified USDA
organic. So
yeah,
pink salt. What might pink salt be, Rho?
I've heard I've heard good and bad
things about the pink salt. What's wrong
with the pink salt? Shout out to Jesse
Gell. God bless you, bro. I'm glad to
see you here, man. Your food bill is
around 250 lbs a week since co, [music]
you know, I have to say as a as an
American, I don't even know what that
means, bro. 250 lbs for me, that's like,
you know, two plates and and and and a
10 and a 20 and a 2.5 on each side.
That's what 250 lbs is in my mind. Is
that [music] kind of like $250?
Or is that more than $250?
Yeah, I know. Food prices have
skyrocketed since co.
It's It's actually pretty crazy. It is
crazy. Especially meat. Meat is so
expensive. Like I know like whenever we
cater like some kind of party or
whatever,
it is insane how much money we pay if
like we're going to get like roast beef
or whatever. It's insane. it. It's like
close to $1,000 if you're going to be
catering a party to like serve like 30
people.
You're going to get like roast beef,
not like the sandwiches, but the actual
like roast beef. It's like $600 700.
It's insane. It's insane.
Yeah. Anything certified doesn't
necessarily mean it's healthy. Like it
just means that they went through the
loopholes
and you pay more for it.
Jesse's paying €200 a week for food
before I had 120 or Yeah, that's crazy,
man.
See, I'm so like isolated from food
prices because I haven't bought eggs
in so long, you know? I like all my
potatoes, all my squashes, like pretty
much most of the stuff I eat.
Not most of the stuff. I shouldn't say
most stuff. A lot of the stuff I eat, we
produce it ourselves.
And then
for the most part, like those fancy
things I showed you, like we don't eat
that all the time. So, we're going to
buy it. It's expensive.
But I think growing your own food really
does a good a good uh job of cutting
into your total food expenses.
It looks like flesh of some sort, like
muscle tissue.
Pink salt might be putrified giants.
That's crazy, huh? I wonder if that's
true.
You know,
cattle has a nice weekly bottom. I keep
hearing that the price of meat is going
to keep skyrocketing because of all the
strange things that have been happening
with like ranchers and all this.
Wouldn't surprise me.
Petrified giants.
Pink salt is petrified giants. I'll have
to stop with the pink salt. All right.
Um
yeah, we'll have to stop. Okay. So, what
we're up we're chopping around. We're
chopping around there. There's nothing
too crazy happening here.
Take one chicken from your backyard.
Yeah. I mean,
I haven't raised meat birds in a while,
to be honest.
But, um,
I wanted to do it this year, but I never
I didn't do it. Now, the year's over.
Your nephew has his own vegetable farm.
That's what's up.
You need land to grow food, which is
expensive.
It depends where you're buying the land.
But yeah, land now it's much more
expensive than it used to be. You used
to be able to get land for like $1,000
an acre some places or even less in the
US. I don't know if you can still do
that. But you'd be surprised how much
you can grow on very little space. Like
honestly, I'm on I'm on six acres.
I'm on six acres
and [music] I probably only actually
grow on like one
acre
and I don't even have to have that much
space to be honest with you. I just have
different garden beds that are spread
out.
So, I'm pretty sure on like half an acre
in your typical suburban backyard, you
know, I had friends who lived in
suburbia and their whole backyard was a
garden. Their whole backyard was a
garden. They grew so much food in their
backyard. It was just a fenced in normal
suburban backyard. It wasn't that big at
all.
And their whole entire backyard, I
remember this one year they grew
pumpkins and the pumpkin vine went up a
telephone pole and there was a pumpkin
hanging from the telephone lines.
A giant pumpkin hanging from the
telephone lines. No one could get it. It
eventually did fall.
But uh yeah, you can grow a lot on a on
a little bit. People make it more
complicated than it has to be in my
opinion.
vertical hydroponics.
A lot of people are dealing with square
feet. You could grow a lot of food in
some square footage. Honestly, look, I
used to live in an apartment and we grew
food on the balcony. We grew food on
that balcony. We had a whole bunch of
5gallon buckets full of compost. We were
growing potatoes. We were growing
tomatoes. We're growing zucchini
squashes out there. We're growing onions
out there
on the balcony. You can make it work.
When there's a will, there's a way, man.
When there's a will, there's a way. Let
me tell you,
the Himalayan mountains. Ah, the
Himalayan. [laughter]
Ah, I see. I see, man. Yeah, it sounds
mad conspiratorial.
If I were to buy land again, where would
I look? I don't know. I don't know. I'm
not I'm not tied really.
I don't know. I I've always liked in the
United States. I've always liked I'd
probably stay right around where I am to
be honest. Um
I think West Virginia is the most
beautiful place in the world.
Yeah. Now, we used to grow in an
apartment and then after we lived in an
apartment, we rented the bottom floor of
a house from a guy and and we grew stuff
in his backyard. He said, "Yeah, go for
it." We grew stuff in in suburbia
backyard and then eventually we came out
here.
Shout out to Jesse who quit smoking
cigarettes and weed. Best decision
you've made this year so far.
Congratulations, man. That sounds really
cool to quit smoking cigarettes and
weed.
I quit smoking weed.
I never smoked cigarettes, but
if I had, I would have hoped I would
quit by now, too.
I have some homemade vertical hydroponic
made of plumbing PVC pipe. I get 25 lbs
of cherry tomatoes per six feet
vertical. Footprint is very small. That
is what's up. Zugzug mahogany. That is
awesome. Can't go wrong. Do you make
your own homemade tomato sauce and
ketchup and salsa and all that? That's
what my wife does with all this stuff.
My wife makes a banging green tomato
salsa. It's fermented. It's like a
fermented green tomato salsa. So good.
And she makes the best tomato sauce,
too. She has this weird machine. My wife
has this weird machine. You you put the
tomatoes in the top and you crank this
thing and it it gets all the the tomato
juice and everything except the seeds
goes out into the into the pot and she
boils it down.
That's good stuff.
I thought she was Italian the way she
made that tomato sauce,
you know.
Boom. Doc saying needs to quit vaping
nicotine and weed and drinking and diet
Dr. Peppers. Too many vices.
Yeah, my vices honestly are if if I have
it around, I'm I I can't stop drinking
that Zevia soda. That Stevia sweetened
soda. [music] And then also
if uh if there's gum chewing gum around,
that's also advice of mine, [music]
chewing gum. But I I try not to chew the
kind with aspartamine in it. I chew
[music] the the kind that doesn't have
aspartame in it.
Travy Trade says, "Vices are a
substitute for the dopamine rush you get
from serving God." Yeah, I do believe
that's true. At least in my life, it was
true.
It was true [music] back when I was when
I was heavily involved in different
substances. In hindsight, it was
absolutely just trying to fill that
missing piece that can only be filled
with a relationship with God.
That's 100% true.
But uh nowadays the Zevia advice I think
comes because
it's late at night [music] and I I would
like to eat something but I know if I do
eat something I won't be able to go to
sleep
and then I'll be up until like 11:00
p.m. Then I'll have like a really really
bad day the next day. So instead of
eating something, I'll have a Zevia.
It's kind of like eating something
except you don't have to chew it. And it
has no calories and it tastes kind of
good.
Um,
Nathan and Sons remmineralizing gum. Hm.
I'm going to I'm going to going to go
ahead and text this to myself. Do the
goat.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what's up, bro.
I'm going to uh
actually going to Google search that
right now, man.
Cool, man. Yeah, I'll check it out.
Remineral arriving. That's That's right
up my alley since I do go to a biologic
dentist, the kind that drills your your
cavities, but no novacaane and doesn't
use fluoride.
O, you gained 18 pounds in the last
eight months by not smoking.
Yeah, you know what? Maybe you should
maybe you should get addicted to the
gym, Jesse. Honestly, you should get
addicted to the to the gym.
Is an 8 kg weighted vest enough on a
treadmill if you weigh 71 kg? Well, I
don't know what a kilogram is cuz I'm
American, but I would tell you that
walking is good for you period. And any
amount you can add to your self will
burn more calories. All right? So the
heavier it is, the more calories you'll
burn, right? Sometimes I wear a 100 lb
weighted vest
just to see what it'd be like if I
gained 100 lbs.
It's pretty crazy. Shout out to Make Me
a Millie. God bless you, bro. See you
around, man.
Yeah, any way to vest is fine.
Anything's fine.
Is it time to long the top, Caesar? I
don't know.
A barbell addiction is serious. Yeah, a
barbell addiction is pretty serious,
guys. But I think it is a good addiction
to have addicted to the gym.
You know, I do like the gym. I go to the
gym all the time. I'm in I'm in I'm I'm
in the gym right now. I'm literally at
the gym right now. You know, we got the
the dang hammer strength leg press right
here. We got the dang functional trainer
life fitness right here. You know, got
the dang hammer row right here. Got the
dang Smith machine right here.
Got the dang squat rack right over here.
Got the preacher curl right over here.
Wouldn't be complete without the pec fly
right over here.
You know what I'm saying?
Wouldn't be complete without the dang
rack of dumbbells. You know, I'm always
in the gym. I live in the gym, baby. I
literally live here. This is literally
where I live. I live in the gym.
I live in the gym, baby.
Want to know how can I stop being a
piece of crap? Um,
oh, you're underweight, Jesse. Okay,
then never mind, bro. If you're trying
to gain weight, then that's good, bro.
You were 99 lbs. What? How tall are you,
bro?
Okay. Had to convert to pounds.
Belt squash. Man, I love belt squats,
bro. I have the uh right here, I've got
the uh the Squat Max MD. I don't know if
you can see that. The Squat Max MD. This
belt squat I love. I love this belt
squat right here. The Squat Max MD, man.
[music]
Preacher curls. Yeah. Look, I have a
thing for preaching and I have a thing
for curls. You know what I'm saying?
Christopher says, "I go to the gym every
weekday. I need to put the same focus on
my Bible studies." Look, here's here's a
pro tip.
In the gym, only listen to the audio
Bible.
Only listen to the audio Bible. That's a
pro tip right there.
But uh
>> All right. Well, here's the thing, guys.
Bitcoin is pumping. I was hoping for a
big big big move during this stream, but
looks like we're not going to get it.
And it's it's coming to the place where
I feel like I need to end the stream.
I think I need to end the stream.
So, I'm going to do that.
Maybe maybe in the future we'll have a a
massive move. As soon as I end the
stream, we're going to pump. All right.
So, God bless you guys. I'll see you
later. Peace.